

Software Developer

eyalgolan96@gmail.com
+972505229299
github.com/eyalgolan
eyalgolan.github.io
Kiryat Ono, Israel

Computer Science student, looking for a **software developer student position**. Excited to become a software developer after 5 years of experience as a DevOps engineer. Fast-learner and highly motivated to create quality products that bring value.

EDUCATION

B.Sc. in Computer Science, Bar Ilan University, 2018 – now

GPA: 90 (expected to graduate by March 2022).

Technologies and Skills: Python, C, C++, C#, Unity, Java, SQL, Linux, Git.

Systems Infrastructure Management (Natmam), IDF, 2011

Final score 90.

High-School for Science and the Arts, 2009 – 2011

Graduated with distinction, majored in Computer Science and Biology.

EXPERIENCE

DevOps Engineer, 888Holdings, 2015 – 2017

- Reduced deployment time of a multi-environment system, from 1 day to several minutes, by creating and maintaining automated CI/CD pipelines.
- Created from scratch the disaster recovery environment.
- Managed complex systems consisting of thousands of servers in production environments.
- Studied Docker and Consul and created a POC to integrate them into the organization.
- Worked closely with the development teams.

Technologies and Skills: Python, PowerShell, SQL, Docker, Linux and Windows Servers, IIS, Blue-Green Deployment.

System Engineer, Volunteer Soldier, Mamram, IDF, 2012 – 2015

- Took ownership over a buggy legacy system with thousands of users, documented its architecture, and resolved bottlenecks to reduce its downtime from 20 days to 1 day a year.
- Managed incidents in thousands of servers in production environments.
- Mentored new team members.

Technologies and Skills: Python, Perl, Windows Servers, Microsoft Clusters, Load Balancers, NetApp Storage Infrastructure, VMware EXSi.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Received early promotion to sergeant as one of 5 nominees for the Mamram award of excellence.
- Won second place at Google's Dev4DevCleanWebHackathon (applications for third world countries).

LANGUAGES

Hebrew – Native

• English - Fluent